while we adults are starting to get back
to a normal life Skip's still have to
stay at home and continue with their
online classes in addition to this in
the free time kids are mostly Clou to
the screen watching their favorite
cartoons and playing their games this
enhance train time affects their eyes so
here are some tips to help you date with
us let definite screen time the time
gets spent in front of the screens needs
to be regulated set time for the
cartoons and even starting on the laptop
keep them engaged in other productive
ways like reading stories playing board
games our simple house chores the 2020
game we played this game every time my
kids spend long hours in front of the
screen every 20 minutes take a 20 second
pray and look outside the window at an
object that is far away the max-min rule
before kids start their online lessons
increase the font to the maximum
possible extent and ensure that the
brightness is rightly set consider
adding a blue light filter or anti glare
screen car to the smartphones and
laptops these preparations go a long way
in ensuring a healthy future for a kids